&gt；&gt；steve kinney：但是你在想，我怎么避免绘画呢？
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: But you're thinking,
how do I avoid painting?
当我想在屏幕上获得像素时，这不就是生活的现实吗？
Isn't that fact of life when I'd
like to get pixels on the screen?
这就是你现在的想法，我可以读懂你的思想，结果。
That's you all right now thinking,
I can read your minds, turns out.
我的问题是，让合成器线程处理这些东西。
My thing is, let the Compositor Thread
handle that stuff.
你说，那是什么意思？
You're like, well what does that mean?
所以这里有一些与GPU一起工作的合成器线程真正的东西
So here are some things that compositor
thread that works with the GPU is really
擅长。
good at.
它不擅长绘制位图，但它非常擅长获取
It's not good at drawing bitmaps, but
it's very good at taking a bitmap that
以前画过，画在更多不同的地方，对吧？
was drawn before and drawing it
in more different places, right?
它擅长缩放和旋转位图。
It's good at scaling and rotating bitmaps.
它擅长让它们变得透明，并对它们应用Instagram过滤器。
It's good at making them transparent and
applying Instagram filters to them.
它也擅长挖掘比特币，对吧？
It's also good at mining Bitcoin, right?
你可以在一个合成器线程上做很多事情，你可以在上面发布
There's lots of stuff you can do on
a compositor thread that you can ship on
去吧。
over to it.
所以一般来说，每当我们做这些事情的时候，如果我们能通过
So generally speaking, whenever we're
doing some of these things, if we can pass
把它转移到不太忙的线程，它只有好的，超好的几件事，
it off to the less-busy thread that's
only good, super good at a few things and
而不是在非常繁忙的线程上做那些不太擅长的事情，
not do those on the very busy thread
that's not as good at those things,
我们完全应该这么做。
we should totally do that.
所以浏览器这样做，它创建了这些称为层的东西。
So the browser does that and
it creates these things called layers.
现在这是一个单一的网站，我们有一个粘滞的标题。
Now this is a single website
where we have a sticky header.
在Chrome开发工具的这个小3D视图中，
And in this little 3D view
in the Chrome Dev tools,
你可以看到它在自己的图层上。
you can see that it's on its own layer.
所以，如果你曾经使用过Photoshop，并且你在图层上有一些东西，
So if you've ever used Photoshop and
you have something on a layer and
您可以在不破坏其下方像素的情况下移动它。
you can move it around without
destroying the pixels underneath it.
这是完全相同的概念，对吧？
It's the exact same concept, right?
所以顶部的横杆有点漂浮在上面，而且
So the top bar kinda floats above, and
我们基本上不是在不同的文本上重新绘制顶部栏，
we basically instead of repainting the top
bar over different pieces of text,
我们基本上是将页面的其余部分滑动到它下面。
we're basically sliding the rest
of the page underneath it.
我们可以这样做。
And we can have it like that.
这真的很酷，这就是为什么如果你看着视网膜屏幕
And this is really kinda cool, and it's
why if you are looking at a retina screen
在此之前，当你带着这个去兜风，你看到了这一切的发生，
before when you took this for
a spin and you saw this happening,
你以前没见过颜料，因为它就像视网膜上的自动，
you didn't see the paint before, because
it was like automatically on retina,
它将采取任何位置固定，并将其移动到自己的层。
it will take anything on position
fixed and move it to its own layer.
对，你没有看到，但是
Right, and you didn't see it but
在非视网膜屏幕上，我们不会这样做。
on a non-retina screen, we don't do that.
原因是当你把它移动到它自己的层时，
The reason for
that is when you move it to its own layer,
你丢失了一些像素锯齿，这使得你的字体看起来很平滑，对吗？
you lose some pixel aliasing which
makes your font look smooth, right?
在视网膜上，你永远不会注意到，在非视网膜上，你可能会注意到这一点
On Retina, you will never notice that,
on non-retina you could notice that so
浏览器不会自动执行此操作，并且
the browser doesn't automatically do it,
and
这就是为什么你有不同之处。
that's why you have the difference there.
所以就像，我想知道所有关于如何把东西
So it's like, I wanna know
everything about how to get stuff to
合成器线程。
the compositor thread.
这是不可能的或有用的，因为合成是一种黑客。
That's not possible or useful because
the compositing is kind of a hack.
这不像W3C规范中的那样。
It's not like, in the W3C spec.
Java脚本被规范出来，DOM被规范出来，
Java Script is specced out,
the dom is specced out,
CSS对象模型检查器。
the CSS object model Inspector.
这些东西的行为是有规则的。
There are rules for
how these things behave.
合成在某种程度上是由浏览器完成的，
Compositing is kinda done by browsers,
无论如何，他们希望有权更改它。
however they want with
the rights to change it.
我们只需要知道它的存在，我们将讨论如何
We just need to know that it exists and
we're gonna talk about how to make
向浏览器提出这样的建议：嘿，为什么你要把这层设置为自己的层？
suggestions to the browser like hey, hey,
why do you make this it's own layer?
我想会很好的，对吧？
I think it will be good, right?
浏览器可以选择听我们的或者不听我们的。
And the browser can choose to either
listen to us or not listen to us.
其他类型的用例。
Some other kind of use cases.
我们做我们的事情，这是我们的代码区，有一个并排的代码和
We do our thing, this is our code
area with a side by side code and
然后是Visual Studio端，我们有这样的设置，它可以滑过它。
then the Visual Studio Side and we have
this settings that slides out over it.
所以那会引起一大堆重漆，但是
So that would cause a whole
bunch of repaints, but
因为它是自己的一层，所以它在前面滑出来。
because it's its own layer,
it slides out in front.
完成后我们把它滑回去，你看到的唯一的重新粉刷
We slide it back when it's done,
the only repainting that you saw
有齿轮的转动。
there was the turning of the gear.
然后选择我想要讨论的下拉列表，但jQuery插件没问题
And select to drop down that I wanna talk
about, but jQuery plugin that's fine
是的，这个东西滑出来了，我们不会重新粉刷那些非常酷的部分。
yeah the thing slides out we don't repaint
any of those parts which very cool.
所以好吧，我想通过每件事使用图层，这很好。
So all right I wanna use layers
through everything, that's great.
人们并不是简单地使用图层，对吗？
One does not simply use layers, right?
你可以说我希望这是它自己的一层，你可能不应该。
You can say I want this to be it's
own layer, you probably shouldn't.
稍后我们将讨论原因。
We'll talk about why in a second.
但你并不是真的负责层级。
But you're not really in charge of layers.
那不是你的事。
That's not your thing.
你可以简单地提出建议。
You can simply make recommendations.
浏览器在幕后为您做了一些优化。
There are optimizations that the browser
does for you under the hood.
再说一次，他们没有被指定出来。
Again they're not specced out.
你不能真正控制他们，但你可以影响他们。
You don't really have any control
over them but you can influence.
[笑]你可以在排字师王面前鞠躬。
[LAUGH] You can bow before
the compositor king.
并要求成为一个层，浏览器可以决定是否或
And ask to become a layer and
the browser can decide whether or
不是你配得上成为一名。
not you're worthy of becoming one.
所以开箱即可看到，现在那些顶层的酒吧都有自己的层次，
So out of the box we saw that right now
those top bars got their own layers,
其他一些事情也可以。
a few other things do as well.
页面根对象获得它自己的层，因为您至少需要一个层，
The root object of a page gets its own
layer cuz you need at least one layer,
对，你需要一些东西。
right, you need something.
具有特定CSS位置的对象，如位置固定，
Objects that have specific CSS
positions like position fixed,
所以那就是那个时候，那只是在视网膜上。
so that's when, that's only on Retina.
这就是你看到头标漂浮在上面的时候。
That's when you saw that
header float above.
具有CSS转换的对象，具有溢出的对象
Objects with CSS transforms,
objects that have overflow so
如果他们可以滚动，这些通常是在他们自己的线程上，因为你不想
if they can scroll those are usually
on their own thread cuz you don't wanna
重新粉刷，想保留每个部分，基本上就是从下面滑动。
repaint, wanna keep each part,
just basically slide it from underneath.
一堆东西会有自己的一层，对吧？
A bunch of stuff will get its own layer,
right?
再说一次，这是浏览器的事情。
Again it's a browser thing.
不一定是给你的，但是
It's not necessarily for you, but
它在我们所做的一些工作中真的很有用。
it can be really useful in
some of work that we do.
如果你想知道所有的事情，你可以成为一个优秀的黑客
If you wanna know all the things,
you can be an elite hacker and
去阅读Chromium源代码，然后
go read the Chromium source code, and
看，字面上有一个叫做合成原因的文件。
see, there's literally a file
called compositing reasons.
[笑]你可以坐下来喝杯咖啡或喝一杯，然后坐在那里
[LAUGH] And you can sit down with a cup
of coffee or a drink and sit there and
通读此文件，但一般说来，较短的列表
read through this file but
generally speaking the shorter list that
我之前给你看过可能是个好的开始。
I showed you before is
probably a good start.
因此，不属于compositingasons.h的对象是
So an object that doesn't fall
under compositingreasons.h is
不会有自己的一层，这可能是一件好事。
not going to get its own layer and
that's probably a good thing.
我们以后再谈，对吧？
We'll talk about that, right?
它将与最后一个有价值的元素位于同一层。
It will be on the same layer as
the last element that did get worthy.
所以它会去找它的父母。
So it will go up to its parents.
有人有自己的一层。
Somebody got their own layer.
如果没有人有自己的一层，那么，
If nobody got their own layer, well,
根对象在层的一个平面上，对吗？
the root object is on the layer's
one flat page, right?
它将只是加入上一层，这是有意义的。
It will just join the previous layer,
which makes sense.